<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Days of Famous Artworks</string>
    <string name="number_of_days">Day %s</string>

    <!-- ArtGallery Strings -->
    <string name="art_gallery_title_1">Guanyin Pusa</string>
    <string name="image_description_1">
        Merchants trading in Silk Road goods, South and Central Asian Buddhist
        proselytizers, and pilgrims who had traveled to India to study Buddhism at its source brought countless
        paintings, scriptures, and small bronze sculptures to China and Tibet. These later served as the inspirations
        for works commissioned by local patrons. Few early Chinese and Tibetan bronze sculptures, and even fewer
        Indian prototypes, survive, as later generations melted them down to make coins, weapons, or new icons.
        The fine statues on display here may have been objects of devotion that were set in portable shrines,
        like the Korean example in the case to the right, for worship in lay people’s homes
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_1">Sculpture</string>
    <string name="culture_1">Chinese</string>
    <string name="date_1">early 8th century</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_2">Five Views of an Elephant Combat</string>
    <string name="image_description_2">
        Howard Hodgkin and Terence McInerney, Indian Drawing : An Exhibition Chosen by Howard Hodgkin, exh. cat.,
        Arts Council of Great Britain, London (London, England, 1983), Figure 29 Stuart Cary Welch and Kim Masteller,
        From Mind, Heart, and Hand: Persian, Turkish, and Indian Drawings from the Stuart Cary Welch Collection, exh. cat.,
        Yale University Press (New Haven, 2004), pp. 148-149, no. 48 Christine Temin, Fogg Shows Persian, Turkish, and Indian
        Drawings, brochure, Harvard University Art Museums (Cambridge, MA, Spring 2005), p. 5 Stephan Wolohojian and
        Alvin L. Clark, Jr., Harvard Art Museum/ Handbook, ed. Stephan Wolohojian, Harvard Art Museum (Cambridge, 2008), p. 111
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_2">Drawings</string>
    <string name="culture_2">Indian</string>
    <string name="date_2">c. 1730</string>


    <string name="art_gallery_title_3">A Prince Receives a Water Jug from a Young Woman at a Well</string>
    <string name="image_description_3">
        In this painting, a prince, mounted on a gray-blue horse, approaches an elaborate well complex.
        His status is denoted by his turban with a large plume and his ornate dress. He reaches up to receive a small,
        gold water jug from a young female figure in yellow. Behind her a group of women converse near the mouth of the well.
        One of them holds a string that is connected to a vessel that is currently down the well. Four vessels are lined up
        against the small railing. Rajput Style, Kishangarh School
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_3">Paintings</string>
    <string name="culture_3">Indian</string>
    <string name="date_3">c. 1745</string>


    <string name="art_gallery_title_4">Young Man in a Blue Cloak</string>
    <string name="image_description_4">
        Persian miniatures reflect a profound significance within Islamic and Persian art history.
        These miniature paintings, particularly from the Safavid period under Shah \'Abbas I, exemplify a pinnacle of artistic achievement.
        Artists like Riza-yi Abbasi have left a lasting legacy through their intricate compositions, rich symbolism, and thematic diversity.
        Scholars such as Eric Schroeder, Ivan Stchoukine, and Anthony Welch have illuminated the cultural and historical contexts of these miniatures,
        emphasizing their socio-political relevance.Persian miniatures depict a range of subjects, from courtly scenes to mystical
        narratives, showcasing the breadth of creativity in Safavid Iran. The dispersal and collection of these artworks, as
        explored by Oleg Grabar and David Roxburgh, highlight their enduring appeal and cross-cultural influence.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_4">painting</string>
    <string name="culture_4">Persian</string>
    <string name="date_4">c. 1587</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_5">It\'s the Day for the Garden</string>
    <string name="image_description_5">
        The folio belongs to an illustrated copy of the Divan of Anvari commissioned by the Mughal emperor Akbar (r. 1556-1605)
        in 1588 and in Lahore. The poet Anvari (1126-1189) is considered one of the greatest figures in Persian literature.
        His panegyric in honor of the Seljuq sultan, Ahmad Sanjar (r. 1118-1157) earned him royal favor and the patronage of
        two of Sanjar’s successors. Anvari’s poems were collected in a Divan, which contains eulogies, satire, panegyrics,
        and other forms of poetry and prose.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_5">Manuscripts</string>
    <string name="culture_5">Indian, Mughal period</string>
    <string name="date_5">c. 1588</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_6">Angela</string>
    <string name="image_description_6">
        Published in Camera Work, no. 12 (1905). Several of Herzog\'s works, including \"The Banks of Lethe\" and
        \"Twixt the Cup and the Lip,\" were included in Camera Work, and a copy of this issue is
        also in the Fogg\'s photography holdings.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_6">Photographs</string>
    <string name="culture_6">American</string>
    <string name="date_6">1905</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_7">Death with Left Hand Raised</string>
    <string name="image_description_7">
        This statuette depicting a decomposing cadaver armed with a bow and arrows (now lost) is an example of the type of
        “death figure” produced since the mid-16th century that served to remind the viewer of the transience of life and
        earthly pleasures. The snakes emerging from the cadaver’s muscles and skin, signifying the temptation of Adam and Eve,
        and the frogs—symbols of evil spirits—squatting inside the rib cage and on the sculpture’s base emphatically suggest
        the cadaver’s physical and spiritual deterioration.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_7">Sculpture</string>
    <string name="culture_7">German</string>
    <string name="date_7">1600-1650</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_8">Grotesque Head of an "Orator"</string>
    <string name="image_description_8">
        Round head with thick, stubby ears, bulbous nose, partially closed eyes, an open mouth drawn down at the left corner
        and a deeply wrinkled forehead. Figure appears bald, possibly due to a lack or loss of color. Hand modeled.Hard,
        light brown caly with very little mica.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_8">Sculpture</string>
    <string name="culture_8">Greek</string>
    <string name="date_8">323-150 BCE</string>


    <string name="art_gallery_title_9">The Holy Family with the Infant Saint John the Baptist and Saint Elizabeth</string>
    <string name="image_description_9">
        One of a group of five paintings of the Holy Family that Poussin produced between 1648 and 1655,
        this version is distinguished by the extensive landscape and the large bath basin that refers to Christ’s
        later baptism. Poussin emphasized Christ’s humanity by showing him writhing in fear at his mother’s attempt
        to bathe him. He receives firm support from the infant Saint John, who is accompanied by his mother, Saint
        Elizabeth. The classical putti assisting the Virgin could represent the Holy Innocents martyred during King
        Herod’s attempt to kill the infant Jesus. The landscape in this canvas is the most highly developed representation
        of nature in this group of paintings. The large lake, the passerby, the carefully placed structures along the
        water’s edge create a contemplative expanse of natural beauty
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_9">Paintings</string>
    <string name="culture_9">French</string>
    <string name="date_9">1650</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_10">Maharana Bhim Singh of Mewar Returns from a Boar Hunt</string>
    <string name="image_description_10">
        The painting depicts Maharana Bhim Singh of Mewar (r. 1778-1828) returning from a boar hunt with his attendants
        and retinue. The haloed king is mounted on a caparisoned horse holding a pig-sticking spear. He wears a green jama,
        or robe, that is associated with aheria, or the spring hunt, when boars are hunted in Rajasthan. According to Rajasthani
        tradition, it is believed that the outcome of aheria fortetold the fruitfulness of the kingdom for the year ahead. Bhim
        Singh\'s had a successful hunt, alluded to by the several slain wild board strapped to the backs of the camels leading
        the procession. At the bottom corner of the image are two members of the hunting retinue with Saluki hounds,
        which were commonly used during boar hunting for stalking, chasing, and, at times, killing. A facloner is also present
        among the procession.The attendants carry the necessary royal attributes: two attendants carry fly whisks
        while one holds a sun-faced standard, which accompanies any Mewari royal procession. The sun is a symbol of the Mewar
        royal family who believed that they were descendants of it.This painting was executed before Bhim Singh became the
        first maharana of the Princely State of Udaipur.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_10">Paintings</string>
    <string name="culture_10">Indian</string>
    <string name="date_10">c. 1810</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_11">Kneeling Female Figure</string>
    <string name="image_description_11">
        Aztec sculptors used specific formal and aesthetic conventions to depict the human figure.
        Seated female figures are usually shown with their legs tucked under them, their feet turned
        inward so that in the back their toes are touching. Their hands rest on their knees. This sculpture
        depicts an elegant Aztec lady wearing a short, simple skirt fastened around the waist with a knotted belt
        worked in low relief. She wears no upper garment. Circular ornaments bedeck her ears. Her hair is wound about
        her head in two strands and held at the top. Her face has delicate rounded contours and is gently animated.
        The eyes and mouth are shown as recessed ovals which once contained inlays. Sculptures of females without any
        deity attributes are rare in Aztec art. It is possible that this figure was dressed on specific days of the
        ritual calendar in deity costumes made of cloth and/or other perishable materials.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_11"> Stone-Sculpture</string>
    <string name="culture_11">Aztec</string>
    <string name="date_11">15th–early 16th century</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_12">King of Navarre</string>
    <string name="image_description_12">
        Léonard Limosin was the greatest enamel painter working in the style of the School of Fontainebleau,
        Italian Mannerists and French artists active at the French court from about 1530 to 1570. Limosin\'s
        enameled portraits are numerous, and he has been ranked, along with Jean Clouet (1486–1540) and Corneille
        de Lyon (before 1500–1574), as the best portrait painter of Renaissance France. This plaque, one of at least
        six based on a drawing attributed to Limosin (Bibliothèque Nationale, Paris), portrays the brother-in-law of
        the French king, François I (1497–1547), who ruled the independent kingdom of Navarre from 1518 until 1555.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_12">Enamels </string>
    <string name="culture_12">French, Limoges</string>
    <string name="date_12">1556</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_13">Bar</string>
    <string name="image_description_13">
        In 1947, Christian Dior presented a collection of wasp-waisted and hip-padded designs.
        The American press immediately dubbed it the \"New Look.\" The collection was a repudiation
        of the styles of the 1920s and 1930s, and it was also clearly indebted to the styles and body-shapers
        of the late nineteenth century. \"The Bar Suit\" was considered the most iconic model in the collection,
        manifesting all the attributes of Dior\'s dramatic atavism.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_13">Cloths </string>
    <string name="culture_13">French</string>
    <string name="date_13">1958</string>



    <string name="art_gallery_title_14">Melencolia I</string>
    <string name="image_description_14">
        Dürer\'s Melencolia I is one of three large prints of 1513 and 1514 known as his Meisterstiche (master engravings).
        The other two are Knight, Death, and the Devil (43.106.2) and Saint Jerome in His Study (19.73.68).
        The three are in no way a series, but they do correspond to the three kinds of virtue in medieval scholasticism—moral,
        theological, and intellectual—and they embody the complexity of Dürer\'s thought and that of his age.
        Melencolia I is a depiction of the intellectual situation of the artist and is thus, by extension,
        a spiritual self-portrait of Dürer. In medieval philosophy each individual was thought to be dominated by
        one of the four humors; melancholy, associated with black gall, was the least desirable of the four,
        and melancholics were considered the most likely to succumb to insanity. Renaissance thought, however,
        also linked melancholy with creative genius; thus, at the same time that this idea changed the status of this humor,
        it made the self-conscious artist aware that his gift came with terrible risks.The winged personification of Melancholy,
        seated dejectedly with her head resting on her hand, holds a caliper and is surrounded by other tools associated with
        geometry, the one of the seven liberal arts that underlies artistic creation—and the one through which Dürer,
        probably more than most artists, hoped to approach perfection in his own work. An influential treatise,
        the De Occulta Philosophia of Cornelius Agrippa of Nettesheim, almost certainly known to Dürer, probably holds
        the explanation for the number I in the title: creativity in the arts was the realm of the imagination,
        considered the first and lowest in the hierarchy of the three categories of genius. The next was the realm of reason,
        and the highest the realm of spirit. It is ironic that this image of the artist paralyzed and powerless exemplifies
        Dürer\'s own artistic power at its superlative height.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_14">Prints </string>
    <string name="culture_14">German</string>
    <string name="date_14">1958</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_15">Now!</string>
    <string name="image_description_15">
        Fuss\'s outsized photogram records time and energy rather than material form. His large sheet of photographic paper,
        floating in a tray of water, was exposed to a bright flash of light at the very moment—Now!—when he splashed a
        bucket of water onto it. The plunging of the water on the paper\'s \"landscape\" and the rippling concentric waves
        and myriad individual droplets on the water\'s surface were all recorded on Fuss\'s sheet, but the abstract pattern
        seems rather to record the birth of a solar system or the splitting of atoms.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_15">Photographs </string>
    <string name="culture_15">New York</string>
    <string name="date_15">1988</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_16">Clarinet in B-flat</string>
    <string name="image_description_16">
        The ivory body of this clarinet and its ornate gold plated keys suggest that it was a special
        commission or presentation piece. Its bell proclaims Sax’s status as musical instrument maker to
        the court of the Kingdom of the Netherlands. This instrument is also distinguished by its early
        use of Ivan Müller’s improved thirteen-key system, which became the preferred choice of most clarinet
        players until the beginning of the twentieth century.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_16">Aerophone-Reed Vibrated-single reed cylindrical </string>
    <string name="culture_16">Brussels, Belgium</string>
    <string name="date_16">1830</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_17">Bronze statuette of a young woman</string>
    <string name="image_description_17">
        This statue, perhaps the best-known Etruscan figural bronze in the Museum\'s collection,
        was produced at one of the major bronze working centers, probably Vulci or Chiusi.
        The artist was clearly inspired by archaic Greek korai, votive statues of young women,
        a connection especially noticeable in the typical frontal pose with right hand extended
        and left hand holding the garment. However, the sculptor was not especially concerned about
        the accurate depiction of costume. The Greek himation (cloak), for example, is misrepresented.
        The folds so prominently visible from the front are absent on the back of the statue, perhaps
        an indication that the artist was looking at a two-dimensional source such as a relief sculpture
        or vase painting rather than a sculpture in the round. In any case, he clearly was more interested
        in rich surface embellishment than in realistic rendering of drapery and produced a wealth
        of engraved details in the hair, jewelry, sewn seams, decorated hems, and drapery folds.
        The pointed shoes (calcei repandi), here elaborately rendered with meticulously detailed
        laces and floral ornament, are distinctively Etruscan. The figure\'s left foot is a modern restoration.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_17">Bronzes </string>
    <string name="culture_17">Etruscan</string>
    <string name="date_17"> late 6th century BCE</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_18">Bronze head of a griffin</string>
    <string name="image_description_18">
        Bronze cauldrons set on tripods or conical stands were among the most spectacular votive gifts dedicated
        in Greek sanctuaries from the eighth to the sixth centuries B.C. Cast-bronze griffins\'
        heads often decorated the cauldron rims; they projected outward from the shoulder of the vessel
        on long necks made of hammered or cast bronze. Some of the dedicated cauldrons were colossal.
        The Greek historian Herodotus describes one made for King Kroisos of Lydia that could hold 2,700
        gallons and another dedicated on the island of Samos that was supported by huge kneeling figures.
        Over six hundred bronze griffins\' heads from cauldrons are known today; most have been found at the
        sanctuary of Zeus at Olympia or at that of Hera on Samos. This enormous head is one of the finest.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_18">Bronzes </string>
    <string name="culture_18">Greek</string>
    <string name="date_18"> third quarter of the 7th century BCE</string>


    <string name="art_gallery_title_19">The Love Song</string>
    <string name="image_description_19">
        Burne-Jones exhibited this painting with the lyrics "Alas, I know a love song, / Sad or happy,
        each in turn." Cupid, with arrows slung over his shoulder, pumps the organ at right. Burne-Jones
        associated the scene with his affair with artist and model Maria Zambaco (1843–1914). More broadly,
        the picture reflects the embrace of music as a model for art that appeals directly to the emotions.
        As one critic said of this painting, "There is no story: nothing to guess at, but everything to feel.
        "It was first owned by businessman William Graham, who commissioned the Small Briar Rose series displayed nearby.
        Also on view are works by, and a bust of, Puvis de Chavannes, who championed Burne-Jones’s art in France.
        Their shared devotion to an idealized and dreamlike past earned Puvis the moniker "the French Burne-Jones."
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_19">Paintings </string>
    <string name="culture_19">British</string>
    <string name="date_19"> 1868–77</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_20">Folio from the \"Blue Qur\'an\"</string>
    <string name="image_description_20">
        This folio comes from a sumptuous, multi volume Qur\'an with indigo pages and silver verse markers that was probably
        copied in North Africa. Its palette is thought to refer to the purple‑dyed, gilded manuscripts made in the
        neighboring Byzantine empire. As in other early Qur\'ans, the script here is difficult to read because the
        letters have been manipulated to make each line the same length, and the marks necessary to distinguish between
        letters have been omitted.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_20">Codices </string>
    <string name="culture_20">Made in Tunisia</string>
    <string name="date_20"> second half 9th–mid-10th century</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_21">Set of jewelry</string>
    <string name="image_description_21">
        he tomb group represents one of the richest and most impressive sets of Etruscan jewelry ever found.
        It comprises a splendid gold and glass pendant necklace, a pair of gold and rock-crystal disk earrings,
        a gold dress fastener (fibula) decorated with a sphinx, a pair of plain gold fibulae, a gold dress pin,
        and five finger rings. Two of the rings have engraved scarabs that revolve on a swivel bezel; one is decorated
        with embossed satyr heads, and the other two have decorated gold bezels.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_21">Etruscan </string>
    <string name="culture_21">Unknown</string>
    <string name="date_21"> Late Archaic</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_22">Wheat Fields</string>
    <string name="image_description_22">
        Twenty-seven views of fields by Ruisdael survive today. In this celebrated example, the artist used the building
        blocks of land, sky, and sea to create an imposing vision of cultivated nature. On the road before us, a man with a
        traveler’s pack approaches a woman and child, while the cumulus clouds dominating the sky add their own element of
        drama. A glimpse of boats at sea on the far left knits this quintessentially Dutch landscape into the wider world.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_22">Paintings </string>
    <string name="culture_22">Dutch, Amsterdam</string>
    <string name="date_22"> ca. 1670</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_23">Madonna and Child</string>
    <string name="image_description_23">
        The Madonna and Child are shown in a contemporary Florentine palace. Through the window is an arcade with the
        armorial device of the wealthy Florentine banker Filippo Strozzi (three crescents). The background evokes the
        area around the Strozzi villa near Florence. A Black man can be seen on a bridge spearing fish,
        and outside a house a Black woman performs domestic tasks. Enslaved people from sub-Saharan Africa
        began arriving in Florence through Portugal in the 1460s, and documents record the presence of enslaved people
        in Strozzi\’s household.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_23">Paintings </string>
    <string name="culture_23">Italian</string>
    <string name="date_23"> ca. 1483–84</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_24">A Pair of Royal Earrings</string>
    <string name="image_description_24">
        The place of these earrings in the history of Indian art is assured, not only for their intrinsic beauty but also
        because of the light they shed on the superb quality of goldsmithing early in this region. Early Indian statues
        of both male and female figures were usually portrayed wearing elaborate jewelry that sometimes seemed fanciful,
        since very little comparable jewelry from that period survives. The discovery of this pair of earrings provided the
        first tangible evidence that the jewelry depicted by sculptors was in fact based on real models,
        for a very similar pair is shown on a first century B.C. relief portrait of a \"Universal Ruler\" (chakravartin),
        from Jaggayapeta.These earrings, judging from their material worth, excellence of craftsmanship,
        and use of royal emblems (a winged lion and an elephant) as part of their design, were most probably made as
        royal commissions. Each earring is composed of two rectangular, budlike forms growing outward from a central,
        double-stemmed tendril. The elephant and the lion of repoussé gold are consummately detailed, using granules,
        snippets of wire and sheet, and individually forged and hammered pieces of gold. The two pieces are not exactly
        identical: on the underside they are both decorated with a classical early Indian design of a vase containing
        three palmettes, but the patterning of the fronds differentiates them. They are so large and heavy that they must
        have distended the earlobes and rested on the shoulders of the wearer, like the pair worn by the \"Universal Ruler.\"
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_24">Jewelry </string>
    <string name="culture_24">India (probably Andhra Pradesh)</string>
    <string name="date_24"> ca. 1st century BCE</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_25">Krishna and Balarama Fight the Evil King </string>
    <string name="image_description_25">
       Kamsa sent Canura and Mushthika, two mountainlike wrestlers who had limbs as strong as lightning,
        to confront the youthful Krishna and Balarama. The climactic moment is statically presented with
        great formal drama. Such scenes of conflict serve as metaphors for Krishna’s destruction of corruption.
        The deep brown background and brightly lit action set against a night sky are typical of the fully developed
        Malwa aesthetic. (This page is from the same manuscript as 1974.116.)
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_25">Paintings </string>
    <string name="culture_25">India (Madhya Pradesh, Malwa)</string>
    <string name="date_25"> ca. 1650</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_26">Portrait of Alain de Coëtivy (1407–1474) </string>
    <string name="image_description_26">
       An outstanding and rare survival of a fifteenth-century French work on paper, this drawing is the work of painter
        and illuminator Jean Fouquet, whose home city of Tours was the preferred residence of the French royal court.
        It is inscribed, \"a Roman legate of our Holy Father in France.\" Recent scholarship by Claudia Märtel has plausibly
        proposed the subject as Alain (IV) de Coëtivy (1407–1474), Cardinal of Saint Praxedes in Rome from 1448.
        He acted as papal legate of Callixtus III to France from 1451–53 and from 1454–55.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_26">Drawings </string>
    <string name="culture_26">French</string>
    <string name="date_26"> ca. 1451–55</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_27"> Christ Crucified between the Two Thieves: The Three Crosses </string>
    <string name="image_description_27">
       The Three Crosses, one of Rembrandt\'s finest works in any medium, represents the culmination of his virtuosity as
        a printmaker. He drew on the copperplate entirely in drypoint which allowed him to fully exploit the velvety areas
        of burr raised by the drypoint tool as it cut into the copper. When Rembrandt created this impression,
        he deliberately left ink on the printing plate; it lightly veils the figures standing at the foot of the cross
        on the right; a thicker layer almost completely covers the bushes along the right edge. By creatively inking the
        copperplate, Rembrandt in a certain sense painted each impression. Each time he printed the copperplate he created
        a unique work. He further varied impressions by printing them on different supports; this impression is printed on
        vellum, which infuses the composition with a warm light. Vellum, less absorbent than paper, holds ink on the
        surface, softening lines and enhancing the richness of entire effect.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_27">Prints </string>
    <string name="culture_27">Christian</string>
    <string name="date_27"> 1653</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_28"> Shah Jahan on a Terrace, Holding a Pendant Set With His Portrait </string>
    <string name="image_description_28">
       The presentation of the emperor amplifies the formula evolved during the reigns of Akbar and Jahangir.
        Shah Jahan is exquisitely dressed and richly adorned with jewels, his imperial rank emphasized by his
        radiating halo and the hovering angels borrowed from European art. The skills of many craftsmen and designers
        of the Mughal court—jewelers, weavers, architects, feather workers, armorers, stonecutters,
        and others—are represented here. This is Chitarman’s earliest dated picture, painted soon after Shah Jahan’s
        accession.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_28">Codices </string>
    <string name="culture_28">Attributed to India</string>
    <string name="date_28"> 1627–28</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_29"> Bone book, E. K.</string>
    <string name="image_description_29">
       Realistic closed book charm, incised in a traditional bookbinding design with four large corners on both covers.
        The lines which make the borders and corners are filled with red wax; decorative dots, central motifs are
        filled with black wax. The front cover has the \"E.K\" and the back has two intersecting curves,
        similar to an infinity motif. The rounded spine has two raised bands, one thick (top), one thin (bottom).
        \-\-description by Mindell Dubansky in consultation with Lynn Heckman
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_29">Ancient </string>
    <string name="culture_29">Unknown</string>
    <string name="date_29"> between 1800 and 1899</string>

    <string name="art_gallery_title_30">The Free Man\'s Companion </string>
    <string name="image_description_30">
      This page from an anthology of Persian poetry illustrates a poem about the moon as it enters the houses of all
        twelve zodiac signs. In the three scenes here, the moon is shown visiting Gemini, depicted as two youths with
        joined, reptile like tails, then in the house of Cancer, a large, scaly crab, and finally seated next to the
        lion of Leo.
    </string>
    <string name="work_type_30">Codices </string>
    <string name="culture_30">Iranian</string>
    <string name="date_30"> dated 741 AH/1340–41 CE</string>


</resources>